var trivia = [{
    "question": "Who won the first ever SuperBowl?",
    "answer1": "Kansas City Chiefs",
    "answer2": "New York Giants",
    "answer3": "Green Bay Packers",
    "answer4": "Dallas Cowboys",
    "correctAnswer": "3"
    
},{
    "question": "Who holds the all time NFL rushing record?",
        "answer1": "OJ Simpson",
        "answer2": "LaDanian Tomlinson",
        "answer3": "Marcus Allen",
        "answer4": "Emmit Smith",
        "correctAnswer": "4"
},{
    "question": "What Quarterback has played in the most SuperBowls?",
        "answer1": "Tom Brady",
        "answer2": "Joe Montana",
        "answer3": "Troy Aikman",
        "answer4": "Bart Starr",
        "correctAnswer": "1"
},{
    "question": "Who has the most recieving yards all time?",
        "answer1": "Steve Largent",
        "answer2": "Jerry Rice",
        "answer3": "Julio Jones",
        "answer4": "Don Hutson",
        "correctAnswer": "2"
},{
    "question": "Who has the most wins as a head coach in the NFL?",
        "answer1": "George Halas",
        "answer2": "Curly Lambeau",
        "answer3": "Tom Landry",
        "answer4": "Don Shula",
        "correctAnswer": "4"
},{
    "question": "Who was the last non-quarterback to win NFL MVP?",
        "answer1": "Adrian Peterson",
        "answer2": "JJ Watt",
        "answer3": "Shaun Alexander",
        "answer4": "LaDainian Tomlinson",
        "correctAnswer": "1"
},{
    "question": "Who holds the best rookie passer rating in NFL history?",
        "answer1": "Dak Prescott",
        "answer2": "Tom Brady",
        "answer3": "Dan Marino",
        "answer4": "Robert Griffin III",
        "correctAnswer": "1"
},{
    "question": "Which NFL team features a helmet decal only on one side of the helmet?",
        "answer1": "Houston Texans",
        "answer2": "Oakland Raiders",
        "answer3": "Pittsburgh Steelers",
        "answer4": "New York Jets",
        "correctAnswer": "3"
},{
    "question": "What is the oldest NFL franchise in continuous operation with the same name in the same location?",
        "answer1": "Cleveland Browns",
        "answer2": "New York Giants",
        "answer3": "Green Bay Packers",
        "answer4": "Chicago Bears",
        "correctAnswer": "3"
},{
    "question": "What NFL team scored the most points in a single SuperBowl?",
        "answer1": "Dallas Cowboys",
        "answer2": "New England Patriots",
        "answer3": "Denver Broncos",
        "answer4": "San Francisco 49ers",
        "correctAnswer": "4"
},













]